Guide to the Transport Workers Union of America: Records of Locals WAG.234
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Records of Other TWU Locals, 1937-1977.
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1944 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1946 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1948 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Local 234: Clippings - I, 1949 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Local 234: Clippings - II, 1949 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1953 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1954 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1955 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1956 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1957 (Box 87, Folder 12a)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1958 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1959 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1960 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1962 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1963 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1964 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1965 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1966 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1975 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Local 235 (Mobile, AL), 1943-1945 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Local 236 (Chicago, IL), 1943-1944 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Local 236, 1945-1946 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Local 236, 1947-1949 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Local 236, 1950-1953 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Local 236, 1954-1955 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Local 236: Agreements: 1942; 1946; 1949; 1951, 1942-1951 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Local 236: Agreements, 1952, 1953 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Local 237 (Jersey City, NJ), 1943-1946 (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Local 237, 1947-1959 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Local 237, 1961-1970 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Local 237: Agreements, 1944, 1960 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Local 238 (Winston-Salem, NC), 1943-1945 (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - Local 239 (Norristown,PA), 1943-1954 (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - Local 239: Agreements, 1945, 1946, 1947 (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - Local 240 (Hansfield, OH), 1944 (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - Local 240: NYC Police Organizing Committee, 1951 (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - Local 241 (New York City, NY), 1943-1944 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Local 241, 1945 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Local 241, 1946-1947 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Local 241, 1948-1950 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Local 241, 1951-1953 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Local 241, 1954-1969 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Local 241, 1970-1973 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Local 241: Agreements, 1943-1946 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Local 241: Agreements, 1947-1954 (Box 89, Folder 8a)
  - Local 241: Agreements, 1957-1967 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Local 241: Agreements, 1968-1973 (Box 89, Folder 9a)
  - Local 242 (Huntington, WV), 1944-1946 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Local 242: Agreements, 1944 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Local 243 (Lynchburg, VA), 1944 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Local 244 (Lacrosse, WI), 1944-1945 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Local 244: Agreements, 1944, 1945 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Local 245 (Omaha, NB): Utilities Division, 1945 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Local 246 (NYC, NY): Ambulance Drivers, 1945 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Local 247 (Columbus, OH): Taxi Division, 1945 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Local 248 (Winston-Salem, NC), 1946-1950 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - Local 248, 1951-1957 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - Local 248, 1958-1973 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Local 248: Agreements, 1950-1953 (Box 89, Folder 20a)
  - Local 249 (Jeannette, PA), 1946-1956 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Local 250 (San Francisco, CA), 1945 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Local 250, 1946-1948 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Local 250, 1949 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Local 250, 1950 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Local 250, 1951-1952 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Local 250, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Local 250, Jan 1954-Jul 1954 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Local 250, Aug 1954-Dec 1954 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Local 250, Jan 1955-Aug 1955 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Local 250, Aug 1955-Dec 1955 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Local 250, Jan 1956-Apr 1956 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Local 250, May 1956-Sep 1956 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Local 250, Oct 1956-Dec 1956 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Local 250, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Local 250, 1958-1959 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Local 250, 1960-1962 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Local 250, 1963 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Local 250, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 17a)
  - Local 250, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Local 250, 1966 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Local 250, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Local 250, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Local 250 (I), 1969 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Local 250 (II), 1969 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Local 250 (III), 1969 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Local 250 (I), 1970 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Local 250 (II), 1970 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Local 250 (III), 1970 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Local 250 (IV), 1970 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Local 250 (V), 1970 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Local 250, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Local 250, Jan 1972-Mar 1972 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Local 250, Apr 1972-May 1972 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Local 250, Jun 1972-Aug 1972 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Local 250, Sep 1972-Dec 1972 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Local 250, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Local 250, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Local 250, 1975 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Local 250, 1976-1978 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Local 250: Agreements, 1962-1968 (Box 92, Folder 9a)
  - Local 251 (San Francisco, CA), 1945-1949 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Local 252 (Nassau/Suffolk Co., NY), 1940-1942, 1946-1949 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Local 252, 1950 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Local 252, 1951 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Local 252, 1952-1958 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Local 252, 1959 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Local 252, 1960-1963 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Local 252, 1964-1967 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Local 252, 1968-1969 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Local 252, 1970-1972 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Local 252, 1973-1977 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Local 252: Agreements, 1940-1944 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Local 252: Agreements, 1945-1949 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Local 252: Agreements, 1950-1958 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Local 252: Agreements, 1960-1965 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Local 252: Agreements, 1966-1969 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Local 252: Agreements, 1970-1974 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Local 253 (New Haven, CT), 1946 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Local 254 (Picher, OK), 1946 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Local 256 (Chicago, IL), 1946 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Local 257 (Miami, FL), 1947-1949 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Local 257, 1950-1968 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Local 257: Agreements, 1949-1953 (Box 93, Folder 14A)
  - Local 257: Agreements, 1958-1968 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Local 258 (NYC), 1947-1949 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Local 259 (Sioux City, Iowa), 1947-1963 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Local 259: Agreements, 1947, 1953, 1960 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Local 260 (Houston, TX), 1946-1948 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Local 260, 1949 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Local 260, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Local 260, 1952-1959 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Local 260, 1957-1959 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Local 260, 1960-1961 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Local 260, 1962-1967 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Local 260, 1968-1973 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Local 260, 1974-1977 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Local 260: Transcript of Hearings - Dispute with Houston Transit Company (I), 1950- (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Local 260: Transcript of Hearings (II), 1950- (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Local 260: Transcript of Hearings (III), 1950- (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Local 260: Agreements, 1947-1950, 1957 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Local 260: Agreements, 1961-1966 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Local 260: Agreements, 1968-1970 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Local 260: Agreements, 1974-1977 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Local 261 (Laredo, TX), 1947 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Local 262 (Pittsburgh, PA), 1947-1950 (Box not specified, Folder 3)
  - Local 262, 1951-1953 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Local 262, 1955-1959 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Local 262, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Local 262: Agreements, 1947, 1950-1958 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Local 263 (Los Angeles, CA), 1947-1950 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Local 264 (NY, NY), 1947-1972 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Local 264: Agreements, 1968, 1970, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Local 265 (Chester, PA), 1947-1960 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Local 265: Agreements, 1947, 1948, 1952 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Local 266 (Portsmouth, OH), 1949 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Local 267 (Upper Darby, PA), 1948-1960 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Local 267, 1961-1973 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Local 267: Agreements, 1948-1970 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Local 268 (McKeesport, PA), 1948-1958 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Local 268, 1959-1972 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Local 268: Agreements: 1948; 1949; 1951; 1952; 1963, 1948-1963 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Local 269 (West Chester, PA), 1948-1969 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Local 269: Agreements, 1948-1970 (Box 95, Folder 20A)
  - Local 270 (LIRR, NY), 1947-1949 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Local 271 (Washington, PA), 1949-1954 (Box not specified, Folder 22)
  - Local 271, 1955-1962 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Local 271: Agreements, 1949-1962 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Local 272 (Salinas, CA), 1949-1953 (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Local 272: Agreements, 1950 (Box 95, Folder 25a)
  - Local 273 (Hudson & Manhattan RR Co, NY), 1947-1949 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Local 273, 1950-1951 (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - Local 273, 1952-1953 (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - Local 273, 1955-1957 (Box 95, Folder 29)
  - Local 273: non-TWU printed contracts, 1941-1948 (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - Local 273: Agreements, 1949-1952 (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - Local 274 (Tampa, FL), 1948-1951 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Local 276 (Waco, TX), 1944-1947 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Local 276, 1949-1954 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Local 276, 1955-1973 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Local 276: Agreements, 1959-1967 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Local 277 (Sherman, TX), 1950-1954 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Local 277: Agreements, 1949 (Box 96, Folder 6a)
  - Local 278 (Pittsburgh, PA), 1950-1953 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Local 279 (Alexandria, LA), 1951 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Local 279, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Local 279, 1953 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Local 280 (Dayton, OH), 1951-1954 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Local 281 (Philadelphia, PA), 1952-1954 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Local 282 (Bristol, PA), 1952-1957 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Local 282, 1958-1973 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Local 282: Agreements, 1951-1964 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Local 282: Agreements, 1965-1973 (Box 96, Folder 15a)
  - Local 283 (New Orleans, LA), 1953 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Local 284 (Washington, D.C.), 1958-1963 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Local 285 (Philadelphia, PA), 1963-1971 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Local 285: Agreements, 1963-1968 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Local 286 (Philadelphia, PA), 1967-1968 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Local 288 (Columbus, OH), 1968-1969 (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Local 289 (Lansdowne, PA), 1968-1969 (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Local 289: Agreements, 1969, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Local 290 (Philadelphia, PA), 1970-1972 (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Local 291 (Miami, Fl), 1969-Jun 1971 (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Local 291, Jul 1971-Dec 1971 (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Local 291, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 27)
  - Local 291, 1973-1976 (Box 96, Folder 28)
  - Local 291: Agreements, 1970-1971 (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - Local 292 (San Francisco, CA), 1970-1971 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Local 292, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Local 292, 1974-1975 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Local 292: Federation News, 1969-1970 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Local 293 (Fort Myers, Fl); dissolved 1976, 1973-1975 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Local 294 (Gainesville, FL); dissolved 1976, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Local 295 (Tallahassee, FL); dissolved 1976, 1973-1975 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Local 296 (Orlando, FL), 1975 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Local 298 (Mariann, FL); dissolved 1976, 1975 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Local 300 (NYC, NY), 1947 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Local 400 (Chicago, IL), 1949-1953 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Local 500 ATD, 1944 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Local 500 ATD, Jan 1945-Mar 1945 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Local 500 ATD, Apr 1945-Dec 1945 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Local 500 ATD, Jan 1946-Jul 1946 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Local 500 ATD, Aug 1946-Dec 1946 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Local 500 ATD, 1947 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Local 500 ATD, 1948 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Local 500 ATD, Jan 1949-May 1949 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Local 500 ATD, Jun 1949 (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - Local 500 ATD, Jul 1949 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Local 500 ATD, Aug 1949-Sep 1949 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Local 500 ATD, Oct 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Local 500 ATD, 1950 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Local 500 ATD, 1951 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Local 500 ATD, 1952 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Local 500 ATD, 1953 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Local 500 ATD, 1954-1958 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Local 500 ATD, 1959-1960 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Local 500 ATD, 1961-1963 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Local 500 ATD, 1964-1968 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Local 500 ATD, 1969-1977 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Local 500 ATD: Contracts, 1945, 1946 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Local 500 ATD: Agreements, 1973, 1975, 1976 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Local 501 ATD, 1945-1949 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Local 501 ATD, 1950-1952 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Local 501 ATD, 1953-1963 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Local 501 ATD, 1964-1966 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Local 501 ATD, 1967-1972 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Local 501 ATD, 1973-1978 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Local 501 ATD: Agreements, 1946, 1947, 1948 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Local 501 ATD: Agreements, 1961-1964 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Local 501 ATD: Agreements, 1964-1966 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Local 501 ATD: Agreements, 1966-1970 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Local 501 ATD: Agreements, 1972-1975 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Local 502 ATD, 1948-1969 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Local 502 ATD, 1970-1984 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Local 503 ATD, 1945-1960 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Local 503 ATD: Agreements, 1955 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1945 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1947-1948 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1949 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1951-1959 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1960-1963 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1964 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1965 (Box 100, Folder 2a)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1966-1967 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1969 (Box 100, Folder 4a)
  - Local 504 ATD, Jan 1970-May 1970 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Local 504 ATD, Jun 1970-Dec 1970 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1971 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1972 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Local 504 ATD, Jan 1973-Jul 1973 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Local 504 ATD, Aug 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Local 504 ATD, Jan 1974-Apr 1974 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Local 504 ATD, May 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 100, Folder 11a)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Local 504 ATD, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Local 504 ATD, Jan 1979-Apr 1979 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Local 504 ATD, May 1979-Jul 1979 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Local 504 ATD, Aug 1979-Sep 1979 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Local 504 ATD, Oct 1979-Dec 1979 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Local 504 ATD: Agreements, 1948-1954 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Local 504 ATD: Agreements, 1955-1959 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Local 504 ATD: Agreements, 1960, 1961 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Local 504 ATD: Agreements, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Local 504 ATD: Agreements, 1963, 1964 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Local 504 ATD: Agreements, 1965, 1966 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Local 504 ATD: Agreements, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Local 504 ATD: Agreements, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Local 504 ATD: Agreements, 1980-1982 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Local 504 ATD: Agreements, 1969-1972 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Local 504 ATD: Agreements, 1973, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Local 504 ATD: Agreements, 1975, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Local 504 ATD: Agreements, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Local 504 ATD: Agreements, 1978, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Local 504 ATD: Arbitration Case, Nov 1973 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Local 504 ATD: Arbitration Case, Dec 1973-May 1974 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Local 504 ATD: Arbitration Cases (misc.), 1973-1974 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Local 505 ATD, 1944-1950 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Local 505 ATD, 1951-1962 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Local 505 ATD, 1963-1966 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Local 505 ATD, 1967-1971 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Local 505 ATD, 1972 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Local 505 ATD, 1973-1974 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Local 505 ATD, 1975-1976 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Local 505 ATD, Jan 1977-Jun 1977 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Local 505 ATD, Jul 1982, 1977-1982 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Local 505 ATD: Agreements, 1950-1966 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Local 505 ATD: Agreements, 1967-1977 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Local 506 ATD, 1945-1961 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Local 507 ATD, 1949-1975 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Local 508 ATD, 1945-1948 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Local 508 ATD: Agreements, 1947 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Local 509 ATD, 1946-1960 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Local 509 ATD: Agreements, 1947-1956 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Local 510 ATD, 1950-1975 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Local 511 ATD, 1947-1949 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Local 511 ATD, 1953-1963 (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - Local 511 ATD, 1964-1975 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - Local 511 ATD: Agreements, 1955, 1961-1969 (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - Local 511 ATD: Agreements, 1970-1974 (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - Local 512 ATD, 1948-1962 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Local 512 ATD, 1964-1975 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Local 512 ATD: Agreements, 1961-1967 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Local 513 ATD, 1949-1969 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Local 513 ATD, 1970-1979 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Local 513 ATD: Agreements, 1960-1978 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Local 514 ATD, 1946-1948 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Local 514 ATD, 1949-1951 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Local 514 ATD, 1952-1953, 1960-1965 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Local 514 ATD, 1966-1967 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Local 514 ATD, 1968-1977 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Local 514 ATD: Agreements, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Local 514 ATD: E.R. Burns Suspension, Aug 12, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Local 514 ATD: E.R. Burns Suspension, Sep 23, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Local 515 ATD, 1946-1973 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Local 515 ATD: Agreements, 1960-1968 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Local 518 ATD, 1947-1973 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Local 518 ATD: Agreements, 1961-1965 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Local 518 ATD: Agreements, 1966, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Local 519 ATD, 1947-1975 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Local 520 ATD, 1947-1953 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Local 520 ATD, 1960-Feb-61 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Local 520 ATD, Feb 1961-Dec 1961 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Local 520 ATD, 1962-1968 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Local 520 ATD: Agreements, 1961, 1964 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Local 521 ATD, 1947-1976 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Local 521 ATD: Agreements, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Local 522 ATD, 1946-1950 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Local 523 ATD, 1947-1950 (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Local 523 ATD, 1956-1969 (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Local 523 ATD Agreements, 1957, 1952, 1965 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Local 524 ATD, 1959-1961 (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Local 525 ATD, 1958-1962 (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - Local 525 ATD, 1963 (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Local 525 ATD, 1964-1969 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Local 525 ATD, 1970-Jul-71 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Local 525 ATD, Aug 1971-Dec 1971 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Local 525 ATD, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Local 525 ATD, 1973-1980 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Local 525 ATD: Agreements, 1960-1966 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Local 525 ATD: Agreements, 1967-1972 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Local 525 ATD: Agreements, 1973-1976 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Local 525 ATD: Agreements, 1978-1980 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Local 526 ATD, 1957-1965 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Local 526 ATD, 1966-1977 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Local 526 ATD: Agreements, 1956-1963 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Local 526 ATD: Agreements, 1964-1973 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Local 526 ATD: Agreements, 1974, 1976, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Local 527 ATD, 1962-1975 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Local 528 ATD, 1965-1973 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Local 528 ATD, 1974-1978 (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - Local 528 ATD: Agreements, 1968, 1973, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Local 528 ATD: Agreements, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Local 530 ATD, 1966-1975 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Local 530 ATD: Agreements: 1968; 1969; 1972; 1973; 1974, 1968-1974 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Local 540 ATD, 1970-1971 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Local 540 ATD, 1972 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Local 540 ATD, 1973-1974 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Local 540 ATD, 1975-1976 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Local 540 ATD, 1977-1980 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Local 540 ATD: Agreements, 1971, 1972, 1973 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Local 540 ATD: Agreements, 1974, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Local 540 ATD: Agreements, 1976, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Local 550 ATD, 1957-1960 (Box 107, Folder 11a)
  - Local 550 ATD, Jan 1961-May 1961 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Local 550 ATD, Jun 1961 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Local 550 ATD, Jul 1961-Aug 1961 (Box not specified, Folder 1)
  - Local 550 ATD, Sep 1961 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Local 550 ATD, Oct 1961 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Local 550 ATD, Nov 1961 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Local 550 ATD, Dec 1961 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Local 550 ATD, 1962 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Local 550 ATD, 1963 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Local 550 ATD, 1964 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Local 550 ATD, 1965 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Local 550 ATD, 1966 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Local 550 ATD, Jan 1967-Apr 1967 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Local 550 ATD, May 1967-Dec 1967 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Local 550 ATD, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Local 550 ATD, Jan 1969-Jul 1969 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Local 550 ATD, Aug 1969-Dec 1969 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Local 550 ATD, Jan 1970-May 1970 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Local 550 ATD, Jun 1970-Dec 1970 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Local 550 ATD, 1971-May 1972 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Local 550 ATD, Jun 1972-Dec 1972 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Local 550 ATD, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Local 550 ATD, 1974 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Local 550 ATD, 1976 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Local 550 ATD: Agreements, 1960 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Local 550 ATD: Agreements (I), 1963 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Local 550 ATD: Agreements (II), 1963 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Local 550 ATD: Agreements, 1964 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Local 550 ATD: Agreements, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Local 550 ATD: Agreements, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Local 550 ATD: Agreements (I), 1967 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Local 550 ATD: Agreements (I), 1967 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Local 550 ATD: Agreements, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Local 550 ATD: Agreements (I), 1970 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Local 550 ATD: Agreements (I), 1970 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Local 550 ATD: Agreements, 1971, 1972 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Local 550 ATD: Agreements, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Local 550 ATD: Agreements, 1976 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Local 550 ATD: Financial Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Local 551 ATD, 1961-1973 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Local 551 ATD, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Local 551 ATD, Jan 1975-Mar 1975 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Local 551 ATD, Apr 1975-Jun 1975 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Local 551 ATD, Jul 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Local 551 ATD, Jan 1976-May 1976 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Local 551 ATD, Jun 1976 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Local 551 ATD, Jul 1, 1976-Jul 25, 1976 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Local 551 ATD, Jul 26, 1976-Jul 30, 1976 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Local 551 ATD, Aug 1976 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Local 551 ATD, Sep 1976-Oct 1976 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Local 551 ATD, Nov 1976 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Local 551 ATD, Dec 1976 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Local 551 ATD, 1977 (Box 112, Folder 1)